哦
Oh.
那个女孩真是个天使 她坚持要我给你这些饼干
That girl is such an Angel. She insisted that I give you these cookies.
妈妈 别吃
[Gasps] Mom! Don't eat those.
我知道我们节日要注意一下碳水化合物摄入量 但这算怎么回事
Now I know we watch our carbs around the holidays, but what was that?
珍妮基尼是个怪物
Jenny Keene is a monster.
耶
Yeah.
前一秒还是“美丽和优雅拥抱”
One minute it's "beauty sharing a hug with Grace".
下一秒就变成“注意你后面”
And the next it's "watch your back".
亲爱的，那不可能
Honey, that can't be true.
刚才在路上 她给我唱“十二天后是圣诞节”
During the ride home, she sang me "the 12 days of Christmas"...
赞美我的鞋子 给我加油钱
Complimented my shoes, and offered me gas money.
哈 她是个骗子 你的鞋很丑
Ha! She's a liar. Your shoes are hideous.
亲爱的
Honey...
想象一下那个小女孩要和丽芙麦蒂同在一个聚光灯下是有多么可怕
Imagine how scared that little girl must be to share a spotlight with Liv Rooney.
是的 我想你是对的
Yeah. [Chuckles] I guess you're right.
在我的阴影里肯定很冷
Must be so cold there in my shadow.
听着 这就是做导师的意义
Look, this is what being a mentor is all about.
那个小女孩需要你的引导
That little girl needs your guidance.
我想每个人在紧张的时候有不同的表现
I guess everybody gets nervous in different ways.
你知道有些人咬指甲
You know some people chew their fingernails,
其他一些人变得跟
and other people turn into a Demon spawn.
好了 让我们打起精神来
Well, let's cheer ourselves up.
我们可以再看一次你爸爸在新闻上一动不动的镜头
We can watch the clip of your Dad freezing up on the news again.
圣诞快乐- Merry Christmas. - [Both laugh]